"data": [
        {
            "question": "John ___ his father.",
            "a": "looks like",
            "b": "looking like",
            "c": "like to",
            "d": "is liking",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Simple present tense: S + V + O \n- If subject singular third person: \n+ V- to be- is, am, are \n+V-to do- + \"s\" or \"es\" (with verb end with ch, -sh, -ss, -x, -o): He watches TV everyday \n- If subject is plural \n+ V- to be: are \n+ V- To do: doesn't need add \"s\" or \"es\": They watch TV everyday ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Up till then, these problems had been ___ for centuries.",
            "a": "laying dormant",
            "b": "laying dormantly",
            "c": "lying dormant",
            "d": "lain dormantly",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Past perfec continous: S + had + been + V_ing",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened? \" The situation is ___.\"",
            "a": "embarrassed",
            "b": "embarrass",
            "c": "much embarrassed",
            "d": "embarrassing",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- We use the past participle, ending in -ed, to modify a noun that is the receiver of the feeling or emotion. \n- We use a present participle, ending in -ing, to modify a noun that is the source (agent or cause) of the feeling or emotion",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hear that you are having a house built. Is it finished yet? \" No, but it is ___ completion.\"",
            "a": "nearly to",
            "b": "almost at",
            "c": "close to",
            "d": "must about it",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Close to: very nearly getting, finding, or achieving something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The reason I didn't go to France was ___ a new job.",
            "a": "because I got",
            "b": "because of getting",
            "c": "due to",
            "d": "that I got",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- That: used as a relative pronoun like 'who', 'whom', or 'which' to introduce a clause",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw the coach on the field after the game, and he seemed ___.",
            "a": "real angry",
            "b": "very angrily",
            "c": "maddening",
            "d": "angry",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- After certain verbs (e.g. be, become, seem, look, taste, smell, sound etc.) the adjective is used, not the adverb ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like Mozart's music very much because his music sounds ___.",
            "a": "sweet and soothing",
            "b": "sweetly and soothingly",
            "c": "sweetingly and soothingly",
            "d": "sweetingly and soothing",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- After certain verbs (e.g. be, become, seem, look, taste, smell, sound etc.) the adjective is used, not the adverb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It seemed to Mary that the butter smelled somewhat ___",
            "a": "bad",
            "b": "badly",
            "c": "worse",
            "d": "worsely",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- After certain verbs (e.g. be, become, seem, look, taste, smell, sound etc.) the adjective is used, not the adverb ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "John Joseph Pershing ___ in 1919, the first highest rank held by any American citizen except George Washington.",
            "a": "to be a full general",
            "b": "he made a full general",
            "c": "made a full general",
            "d": "was being made a full general",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- We use the past simple for completed action in the past",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Controversial matters involving the two groups were discussed; nevertheless, most of the representatives ___.",
            "a": "remaining calm",
            "b": "remained calmly",
            "c": "remain calmly",
            "d": "remained calm",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Remain/stay/keep calm",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "64",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "5"
        }
    ],